- Your wife survived the attack. - Thank God.
- 你的妻子在袭击中幸存下来了  - 感谢上帝
I should never have given in.
我就不应该让步
I should have ordered back the motorcade.
我应该召回车队
The terrorist attack failed.
恐怖分子的袭击失败了
We have to assume they'll make good on their threat to use
我们必须假设他们会在美国境内
the Sentox nerve gas on American soil.
充分利用剩下的Sentox神经毒气
Listen, I made a mistake.
听我说 我犯了一个错误
- I didn't think that I had any choice. - Charles.
- 我想我别无选择  - 查尔斯
You didn't stand up to them.
你没有勇敢地抵抗他们
You saved my life.
是你救了我
You're welcome.
不用谢
Country's lucky to have men like you...
拥有你这样的人真是国家的幸运
I'm lucky.
我很幸运
Mrs. Logan?
洛根夫人?
Christopher Henderson was responsible for setting up
克里斯托夫・亨德森对安排
the deal that allowed the terrorists to gain control of the Sentox.
让恐怖分子得到Sentox毒气的交易付有责任
He left me for dead.
他让我去送死
Right now, Henderson is our primary link.
现在 亨德森是我们最重要的线索
You are going to tell me now how to find the rest of the nerve gas.
你现在就得告诉我怎样才能 找到剩下的那些神经毒气
Do it, Jack. Get it done.
来吧 杰克 动手吧
Shoot me.
朝我开枪
You son of a bitch!
你这个狗娘养的
I shot her above the kneecap.
我打在她的大腿上
- She can still walk. - Son of a bitch!
- 她还能走路的   - 狗娘养的
You make me shoot again,
你逼我再朝她开枪的话
she'll spend the rest of her life in a wheelchair.
她就要在轮椅上过她的下半辈子了
Tell him what he wants to know.
告诉他他想知道的事情吧
I can't.
我不能
I'm bringing Christopher Henderson into CTU.
我马上带克里斯托夫・亨德森去CTU
I need an interrogation room prepped.
准备好一间审讯室
I don't care that you took my wallet.
我不介意你拿了我的钱包
I just need to get my keycard back.
我只想要回我的钥匙卡
It's of no value to you.
你拿去一点用都没有
It just lets me in and out of this building.
它只是我出入这幢大楼用的
Okay, you told me we were just going to take
你跟我说我们只
his cash and a credit card.
拿他的钱和一张信用卡
That's how I'm getting us all this money.
这就是最值钱的信用卡
$20,000 line of credit
值两万美金
right here.
就在这里
Who's going to pay you that kind of money?
谁会给你钱买这东西
- I have the keycard. - How long will it take for you
- 我拿到钥匙卡了  - 你要多长时间
to reprogram it?
才能设置好?
Five minutes, and then we will be able to use it
5分钟 然后CTU的大门就
to access CTU.
敞开了
Good.
很好
The following takes place between 6Pm and 7Pm
以下是发生于傍晚六点至七点之间的故事
Yes.
讲
I'm reprogramming
我正在重新设置
the CTU keycard right now.
那张CTU的钥匙卡
Will it work?
能行吗?
I need to change the ID,
改一下ID即可
but preserve McGill's executive entry privileges.
但保存麦克基尔的访问权限
It won't be a problem.
不会有问题的
Good.
好
Our couriers are delivering the canisters to the targets.
我们的手下正在把毒气罐送往目的地
They'll be in place soon.
他们很快就能就位
When are you launching your attacks?
你什么时候发动袭击?
After you're done at CTU.
在你办完CTU的事之后
I'm a few minutes out.
我挂断电话几分钟
Call me when you're there.
你到那里了就给我打电话
Understood.
明白了
We were able to neutralize the attack on the hospital, sir.
我们消除了医院的袭击威胁 长官
Good.
很好
Do we have any idea
我们知不知道恐怖分子的
what the terrorists' next target might be?
下一个袭击目标是哪里?
We're working with federal and state authorities
我们正在和联邦以及州政府合作
to harden security around the highest-value targets
来加强洛杉矶市重要目标的
in Los Angeles.
警戒工作
In other words, no. We're completely in the dark.
也就是说 我们一无所知
We're just sitting around, waiting for Bierko to hit us again.
我们只是束手无策地 等着比耶科再度袭击我们
We do have one promising lead, sir.
我们还有一条有希望的线索 长官
Jack Bauer was able to recapture the man who escaped,
杰克・鲍尔抓住了逃跑的目标疑犯
Christopher Henderson.
克里斯托夫・亨德森
Henderson was a Defense contractor
在国防部的一个承包商工作
who brokered the sale of the nerve gas to Bierko.
是他促成了把神经毒气卖给比耶科的交易
Is this the same Christopher Henderson who worked at CTU?
就是那个在CTU工作的 克里斯托夫・亨德森吗?
Yes, sir. He was head of Field Ops,
是的 长官 他是外勤行动主管
until Jack brought him down on corruption charges.
直到杰克指控他贪污拉他下台为止
And this Henderson knows how to find Bierko?
这个亨德森知道怎么找到比耶科?
We believe so, but he's not cooperating.
我们认为是这样 但是他不合作
Jack's bringing him in for further interrogation.
杰克现在带他过来做进一步的审讯
Keep me posted on any progress.
有进展就向我报告
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Mr. Buchanan,
布坎南先生
Tony Almeida's been asking to see you down in the Clinic.
托尼・阿尔梅达要求 在下面的医务室见你
I don't have time right now. Tell him I'll get to him as soon as I can.
我现在没时间 告诉他我一有空就去见他
And, Ms. Raines ?
瑞恩斯女士?
Kim Bauer is here.
金・鲍尔来了
She's just clearing Security.
她 刚通过安检
Put her in the Field Ops Office, please.
请让她去外勤行动办公室
Yes, ma'am.
好的 夫人
What's Kim Bauer doing here?
金・鲍尔到这里来做什么?
Jack asked me to call her.
杰克叫我打电话给她的
Does she know?
她知道吗?
Not yet.
还不知道
Who's with her?
跟她在一起的是谁?
I don't know, but I'll find out from Security.
我不知道 但我会从保安那里查的
Excuse me.
抱歉失陪
- This is Bauer. - Hey, it's me.
- 我是鲍尔  - 是我
Is Burke prepped for the medical interrogation?
伯克准备好药物审讯了吗?
Yes.
好了
Jack, Kim just arrived at CTU.
杰克 金刚才到CTU了
- What did you say to her? - Nothing yet.
- 你对她说什么了?  - 什么都还没说
Good. I want her to hear it from me.
很好 我希望由我来向她解释
Jack, it might be easier for her
杰克 要是她在见到你之前
if she knows that you're alive before she sees you.
先知道你还活着 也许会使她好受些
When I first saw you...
当我第一次见到你的时候...
- It's-it's just... - Yeah, I know.
- 那真是...  - 我明白
I-I... I understand.
我 我...我理解那种感受
Look, when you talk to her,
你对她说的时候
just explain that the reason why
只要向对她解释
I couldn't tell her I was still alive was 'cause
我不能告诉她我还活着的原因是
I was trying to protect her.
因为要保护她
Of course, I will.
我当然会
Audrey, thank you.
奥黛丽 谢谢
Kim's at CTU right now.
金现在在CTU?
You know, after you died,
你死了之后
Chase left her, and she hit bottom.
蔡斯离开了她 她情况极为糟糕
Did you know that?
这些你知道吗?
It's only right now she's putting her life back together.
她到现在才重新开始她的生活
Or maybe you did know that,
或许你知道
but you just couldn't do anything about it ?
但是你只是什么也做不了?
This doesn't concern you.
这与你无关
Oh, I think it concerns me, Jack.
我认为跟我有关系 杰克
Miriam and I were there for Kim when you weren't.
你不在的时候  是玛瑞安和我陪在金身边
Whatever you think of me, Miriam and I love that girl.
不管你怎样看我 玛瑞安和我都爱这个女孩子
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
Both my parents died here.
我的父母都死在这里
I swore I'd never come back to this place.
我曾经发誓再也不要回到这里来了
Well, we can leave right now if you want.
你想离开的话 我们现在就走
Here, she's coming.
她来了
Kim.
金
- Hi. - Hi.
- 你好  - 你好
This is Barry Landes.
这位是巴里・兰德斯
- Hi. - Audrey Raines.
- 你好  - 奥黛丽・瑞恩斯
So, what is it?
到底有什么事?
What did you have to tell me that was so important?
你有什么重要的事情必须要告诉我?
I think it would be better if we talked in private.
我认为我们还是私下谈比较好
Whatever you have to say, you can say it in front of Barry.
不管什么事情 都可以当着巴里的面说
- Kim, I really think that that this... - No, no, it's... it's Okay.
- 金 我真的认为这...  - 不 不 没关系
It's about your father.
是关于你的父亲
What about my father?
关于我父亲的什么事?
He's alive.
他还活着
Kim, he wanted to tell you but couldn't, in order to protect you.
金 他想过告诉你  但是为了保护你 他不能这么做
Someone inside the government wanted your father dead,
政府里有人想杀掉你的父亲
so he staged his own death and went underground.
所以他安排了他自己死亡的假象 然后秘密藏匿起来了
He knew, that you wouldn't be safe
他知道要是告诉你他还活着
if he told you that he was alive.
你就会有危险
I didn't know either until this morning.
我也是今天早上才知道的
I thought maybe if I told you now before you saw him,
我觉得要是在你见到他之前告诉你
it might be a little bit easier.
也许会让你好受一些
He's on his way in now to CTU.
他正在赶往CTU的路上
Hello, Mike.
你好 麦克
Mr. Vice President.
副总统先生
I thought you were in Salt Lake City today.
我以为你今天会在盐湖城
Hal canceled his engagements to be here, Mike.
哈尔取消了他原定的安排赶到这里 麦克
I think you'll agree we need all hands on deck
你不会反对动员所有力量
to deal with this Sentox situation.
来处理这次Sentox毒气危机吧?
- Of course, Mr. President. - Okay.
- 当然不是 总统先生  - 好
So, what's on your mind, Hal?
那么 你怎么看 哈尔?
Mr. President, when these terrorists attack,
总统先生 当这些恐怖分子发动袭击的时候
you're going to need to maintain order.
你需要维持良好的社会秩序
And I submit to you,
而且我说出我的看法供您参考
the plan you're implementing with CTU
您和CTU所实施的计划不足以
is inadequate.
应付现状
Sir, it was drawn up after a careful study
长官 这是在仔细研究了
for an attack of just this magnitude.
这样规模的袭击之后制定出来的计划
CTU is already coordinating with first responders.
CTU已经和第一反应部队合作了
Fine, and they should still do so.
很好 他们也应该继续这么做
But what I'm proposing is something far more sweeping.
但是我要提出的 是更大规模的举措
And I believe it's warranted by the facts.
而且我确信这是以事实为依据的
Andrew?
安德鲁?
To begin with,
首先
I'm revising all of CTU's casualty estimates,
我修正了CTU所做的伤亡估计
based on the assumption that the terrorists will hit
假设恐怖分子会袭击
all of these high-profile targets: hospitals,
所有这些高亮标注的目标
malls, sporting arenas, transit hubs.
医院 商业区 体育场 交通枢纽
My low estimate is 400,000 casualties.
我的最低估计是40万伤亡
Now, that's a considerable upward revision.
这数目怎么增加这么多
I'd like to know how you reached it.
我希望知道你是怎么得出这个结论的
Well, you're free to talk to my working group.
你尽可以去咨询我的工作组
You know, frankly, I believe that there are a lot of people
坦白地说 我相信有很多人
who don't take this threat seriously enough.
不把这次威胁当回事
I assure you we're taking it very seriously.
我向你保证 我们正很严肃地处理这件事情
We have no agenda but to do so.
我们没有议程 但是确实在严肃处理这件事
Considering these revised numbers,
考虑到修正后的数据
what's your recommendation?
你有何建议?
Well, I believe you should be thinking
我认为你应当考虑
of a preemptive declaration of martial law
在洛杉矶及其周围地区
in the greater Los Angeles area.
预先宣布戒严
Mr. President,
总统阁下
martial law is appropriate only
戒严令只有万不得已
as a last-ditch measure,
才能采用
not as a preemptive one.
而不能作为预防性措施
Go on.
继续
Every study we've done has shown it would incite more unrest,
我们做过的每一项研究都表明 这只会引发更多的不安情绪
not less.
而不是缓解
And you couldn't do it without approval from Congress.
而且只有国会批准后 你才可以这么做
Which is why we won't call it martial law.
这正是我们不将其称为戒严令的原因
No one is going to play semantics here
当我们派部队上街
when we're putting troops on the street
来避免人们互相残杀的时候
to try to keep people from killing each other.
那时就不会有人在这咬文嚼字了
You're talking about a panic that hasn't happened.
你是要制造一场不存在的恐慌
Right now, the public isn't even aware of a threat.
现在公众甚至还不知道有威胁存在
You declare martial law, you'll have to tell them.
你要宣布戒严 你就得告诉他们
How long would it take to deploy the troops?
部署军队需要多长时间?
I've already been in touch with the Pentagon.
我已经跟五角大楼联系过了
National Guard and Army units are on standby, pending your decision.
国民警卫队和军队各部正在待命  等待您的决定
Mr. President, I agree there's a case
总统先生 我知道必须做出一个决定
to be made, but for God's sake, let's make it to Congress.
但是看在上帝份上 我们务必要通知国会
- We can declare an emergency session... - We don't have time, Mike.
- 我们可以召开国会紧急会议  - 麦克 我们没有时间了
Hal is right. This... This attack could take place any minute.
哈尔说的对  这次袭击随时都可能发生
If CTU can't find this man Bierko, we're going to get hit.
如果CTU不能找到那个叫比耶科的人 我们就会遭到恐怖袭击的
It would be smart to have control of the streets.
控制街道是明智的做法
This is a mistake, Jack.
这是错误的 杰克
You don't want to do this.
你这么做会后悔的
Get out.
出来
I'll get immediate immunity if I talk.
我只要说出来就会立刻得到豁免
You know it, and I know it. And I'm not even going to ask for it.
这一点你明白 我也明白 我甚至不用去要求得到豁免
Damn it, Jack. Will you listen to me?
混账 杰克 你在听我说吗
I'm not trying to protect myself. I'm trying to protect this country.
我不是为了保护自己  我是为了保护这个国家
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
You don't want to know what I know.
你不会希望知道我所知道的事情
You get me to talk, I promise you
我向你保证 你要是让我开口
you'll just be opening Pandora's box.
你就如同开启了潘多拉的魔盒
Tell me, and let me judge that for myself.
告诉我 让我来自己来权衡好了
That's what I thought.
我就是这样想的
I'll set him up in Holding.
我会把他关在禁闭室
Let me know when he's ready for interrogation.
当可以审问他的时候告诉我
- Yes, sir. - Jack.
- 是的 长官  - 杰克
Keycard, please.
请出示通行卡
Oh. All clear, sir.
可以了 先生 请进吧
Yeah.
是的
Okay, I will, thanks.
好的 我会的 谢谢
That was Curtis; he's on his way back from the hospital.
是柯蒂斯打来的  他正在从医院回来的路上
Okay, good.
好的
Audrey.
奥黛丽
Did you speak to Kim?
你跟金谈过了吗?
- Yes. - What was her reaction?
- 是的  - 她有什么反应?
She's a little confused.
她有点困惑不解
You should also know that she's here with someone.
你要知道她是跟另一个人一起来的
I think it might be her boyfriend.
我想那大概是她的男朋友
His name is Barry Landes.
他叫巴里・兰德斯
- Where is she? - She's in the Field Ops Office.
- 她在哪儿?  - 她在外勤行动办公室
- Okay, thanks. - Yeah.
- 好的 谢谢  - 好
I don't know what to say.
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know what you expect me to say.
我不知道你希望我说什么
You don't have to say anything.
你什么也不用说
Why didn't you just tell me you were alive?
你为什么不告诉我你活着?
I couldn't.
我不能说
If you knew I was alive, you would have been at risk.
如果你知道我活着 你早就有危险了
I had no choice.
我别无选择
You could have chosen to trust her.
你应该选择信任她
I'd like to speak with my daughter alone, please.
我希望能跟我女儿单独谈话 劳驾
I don't think that's a good idea.
我认为这不是个好主意
I don't care what you think.
我不在乎你怎么看
I'm sure you don't.
我知道你不在乎
All that matters is you, and the judgments you make.
你只在乎你自己以及你做的判断
Even if it affects those that love you.
即使这会影响那些爱你的人
Kim.
金
Barry, please, let me speak to my dad.
巴里 让我跟我爸爸谈
- I'll be right outside. - Yeah.
- 我就待在门外  - 好的
Don't judge him.
别因此就对他下结论
He was there when no one else was.
大家都不理会我的时候 只有他陪着我
The most painful thing that I've ever been through
我所经历过的最痛心的事情
was having to walk away from you.
就是不得不离开你
Even more painful than losing your mother.
甚至比失去你的母亲还要痛苦
But it was the only way to make sure
但这是确保你安全的
that you would be safe.
唯一办法
I buried you.
我埋葬了你
I... I know.
我...我知道
You know, there's something wrong with people like you.
你知道 像你这样的人有个毛病
You can't hold on to anything.
你不能坚持做任何事情
Chase couldn't either.
蔡斯也不能
He tried for a while, and then he was gone, just like you.
他尝试了一段时间 然后就离开了 就像你一样
And now, you're back...
而现在你回来了...
and I'm just supposed to...
而我就应该表现得...
I'm happy that you're alive.
很高兴得知你还活着
I am.
没错 是这样
But I can't give you what you want right now.
但是我不能立即给你想要的一切
Okay.
好的
I understand that.
我理解
I need you to know that I'm sorry, and I...
我需要你知道我很抱歉 并且我...
Please, just go.
够了 你走吧
Excuse me.
抱歉
Burke needs you in holding.
伯克要你去审讯室
I'll be there in a minute.
我马上就去
I've got to go.
我得走了
Barry's got a conference. We have a plane to catch.
巴里要参加一个会议 我们要去赶飞机了
Please, Kimberly...
金伯莉 别这样...
I want you to stay just a little longer.
我想让你再多呆一会儿
There are some things that I still need to tell you.
我还有些事情需要告诉你
Please?
行吗?
I'll talk to Barry.
我得和巴里商量一下
Fine.
好
I'll be right back.
我很快就回来
You call for me, Tony?
你要见我 托尼?
Yeah.
对
What's going on?
怎么了?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
这正是我要问你的
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
What do you think I mean, Bill?
比尔 你认为我是什么意思?
My wife was killed this morning, right in front of my eyes.
今天早上我的妻子就在我面前被杀害了
And nobody here has told me who did it, or why.
至今没人告诉我 究竟是谁干的或者动机?
The investigation is ongoing, Tony.
调查正在进行 托尼
Come on, Bill.
行了 比尔
I used to work here.
我在这里工作过
I know that's what you say to people
我知道当你们不愿意说出事实的时候
when you don't want to tell them the truth.
你就会这么说
The truth is you're not an agent anymore.
事实是你不再是一名政府特工了
And what you're asking me is classified.
而你问我的事情是机密
Tony, it doesn't matter what I tell you, there's nothing you can do.
托尼 我告诉你什么无关紧要 你对此无能为力
I know there's nothing I can do!
我知道我什么也做不了
Look at me, for God's sake!
看在上帝份上 看着我
I just want to know who did it.
我只想知道是谁干的
I think for the sake of all the years I've given this place,
我想凭我为这个地方奉献了这么多年
and all the sacrifices I've made, I think I deserve to know. Don't you?
以及我所做的所有牺牲的份上 我认为我理应知道 对吗?
All I can tell you is...
我只能这样跟你说...
Michelle's murder was part of a bigger plan...
米歇尔被杀是个大阴谋的一部分...
to supply terrorists with Sentox nerve gas.
向恐怖分子提供Sentox神经毒气
Who's behind it?
是谁主使的?
Who's responsible, Bill?
是谁负责的 比尔?
The highest we've been able to get up the chain of command
我们现在查到的最高指挥人
is someone you might know from when you worked here.
是一个你在这里工作的时候 可能就认识的一个人
Christopher Henderson
克里斯托夫・亨德森
What?
什么?
Why?
为什么?
We're working on it, Tony.
我们正在查 托尼
Don't let him get away with this, Bill.
别让他逃脱惩罚 比尔
Don't you let him cut a deal.
别和他妥协
I won't.
我不会的
What do we know about the man who's with Kim?
你了解跟金在一起的那个男人是什么情况吗?
He's registered with the state as a clinical psychologist.
一个州里的注册临床心理医生
- She was his patient? - I think so, yes.
- 她是他的病人?  - 我猜是的
He's ready.
可以开始了
Whatever he's not telling us is important.
他想保密的消息一定很重要
He knows what's coming.
他知道接下来会发生什么
And he's willing to tolerate an inhuman amount of pain.
而他宁愿忍受非人所能承受的痛苦
Open the door.
开门
Damn it, Christopher.
你妈的 克里斯托夫
I don't think you became a part of this because of self-interest.
我认为你不是因为你的私利 而卷入这件事的
I honestly believe that you think
我真的相信你认为
what you're doing right now is the best thing for this country,
你现在做的事情 是对国家最有益的
but it is not your choice to make.
但这不是由你做决定的事
That's good, Jack.
这很好 杰克
Disarm your subject's resolve by showing empathy,
通过向你的审问对象表示同情
and respect for his agenda.
并表示尊重他的选择来瓦解其决心
This is not a joke.
这不是开玩笑
Thousands of lives are at stake.
成千上万条生命危如累卵
People that we promised to protect, to make feel safe.
是那些我们承诺要保护 并使之有安全感的人们
There is enough time for you to tell me what I need to know
你有足够多的时间来告诉我
to stop this insanity.
怎样来阻止这起疯狂的行径
Please.
别逼我
I'm sorry, Jack. I really am.
很抱歉 杰克 我真的很抱歉
But I can't tell you what you want to know.
但是我不能告诉你 你想知道的事情
Start it.
用刑
Mrs. Logan.
洛根夫人
Mrs. Logan, if I could have a minute.
洛根夫人 我能不能和你说几句话
If this is about Aaron, it doesn't concern you.
如果是有关艾伦的事  那与你无关
No, Mrs. Logan, it doesn't.
不 洛根夫人 不是
And I'm not here to discuss it.
我来这里不是探讨这个问题的
What is it?
那是什么?
The country's facing a crisis.
国家正面临危机
The President needs you.
总统需要你
He, he needs me.
他 真好笑阿
If you think the decision to let the attack
要是你认为他做出让车队受袭的决定
on the motorcade proceed was easy for him, you're wrong.
是轻而易举的话 那么你错了
I was with him when he got down on his knees and prayed.
当时他跪下来祈祷 我就在他身边
He did?
他真的这样做了?
He loves you.
他爱你
He didn't want to lose you.
他不想失去你
But with the lives of so many people in jeopardy,
但是这么多人的生命危在旦夕
he felt he had no choice.
他觉得他别无选择
We've known each other a long time, you and I.
我们彼此了解对方已经很久了
Why don't you stop talking about what a positive influence I am,
不要说诸如我会带来 什么样的积极影响之类的话了
and tell me precisely what it is
告诉我究竟
you're trying to get me to do.
你要我做什么
Vice President Gardner is advising your husband
副总统加德纳尔尔 建议你的丈夫
to declare martial law in Los Angeles
预先在洛杉矶宣布戒严
in preparation for the release of the nerve gas.
来应对释放神经毒气的袭击
He wants to do it without congressional sanction
他不想经过国会批准就这么做
or a timetable to lift it.
也没有时间表定下解除期限
He can't just rewrite the law.
他不能无视法律的存在
- Hal's got an agenda. - Well, he's wrong.
- 哈尔早有预谋的  - 但他是错的
This will make things far worse.
这会使情况变得更糟
Mrs. Logan, all I know is,
洛根夫人 我所知道的是
the President is listening to Hal Gardner.
总统现在听信哈尔・加德纳尔的话
And it will only help the country
只有让他也听信你的话
to have him listening to you as well.
才能对国家有益
No, hold off on deploying units 7 through 12
不 暂停7到12号单位的部署
until we finalize our target scenario.
直到我们确定我们对手的计划
What is it?
什么事?
I was running a channel clearance,
我刚才在做管道检查
and I noticed that one of the environmental systems
我注意到一个环境系统中
put out a trouble flag.
出了问题
It's probably a tech crew changing out a circuit board.
可能是技术人员在更换电路板
That's what I thought, but I logged on to the manifest.
我就是这么想的 但是我登陆到工作计划
There's nothing scheduled.
并没有这样的安排
Carrie, I'm in the middle of coordinating with first responders.
凯莉 我正在协调现第一反应部队
We're on high alert. I don't have time for this.
我们处在高度警戒状态  我没时间管这个
You don't have to snap at me.
你无需这样训斥我
I just thought someone should check it out.
我只是觉得应该有人去检查检查
Then check it out.
那就去检查一下
Carrie.
凯莉
Can you forgive me?
你能原谅我吗?
You acted like the President of the United States.
你做了作为美国总统该做的事
Yes, I did.
是这样
But you wanted me to be your husband first.
但是你希望我首先做我作为一个丈夫该做的事
Can't pretend that I didn't.
这一点我无法否认
I still love you as much as I always did.
我还是像过去一样爱你
Martha.
玛莎
There'll be plenty of time for us later.
以后我们还有很多时间
You have to get back to work.
你必须回去工作
The country needs you
国家比我
more than I do.
更需要你
Hello?
喂?
Anybody working on the system?
有人在整修系统吗?
Chloe.
科洛依
Hi, Kim.
金 你好
You're still here.
你还在这里
Yeah.
是的
Look, my father said that he had to do something.
我父亲说他要办点事情
You know how long he's gonna be?
你知道他要多久才能办完吗?
No, sorry.
不知道 抱歉
Chloe...
科洛依...
I'm kind of busy right now.
我现在有点忙
You knew my father was alive, didn't you?
你以前就知道我父亲活着 是吗?
For a year and a half you've known.
早在一年半以前
Yeah.
是的
He trusted you.
他信任你
Only because he had to; I helped stage his death.
那是他不得已而为之 我帮助他布置了死亡的假象
You don't have to make excuses.
你不需要编造借口
I'm not making excuses.
我不是找借口
Four people knew he was alive, two of them are dead:
有四个人知道他活着 两个已经死了
President Palmer, and Michelle Dessler;
帕默总统和米歇尔・戴斯勒
and Tony Almeida's in serious condition.
托尼・阿尔梅达伤得很严重
Michelle's dead?
米歇尔死了?
The only reason I'm alive is because your dad found me in time.
我还活着的唯一原因是因为 你父亲及时地找到了我
I know this is really hard for you,
我知道这让你很难接受
and it's none of my business,
但是这不是我的事情
but you should try to cut him some slack.
但是你应该给他一个改正的机会
What's going on, Bill?
比尔 怎么了?
Lynn...
林...
What is it?
怎么了?
We just got a call from LAPD.
我们刚刚接到洛杉矶警局的电话
They found your sister's body in her apartment.
他们在你妹妹的公寓里 发现了她的尸体
She'd been shot.
她被枪杀了
What?
什么?
I just talked to her.
我刚刚和她通过电话
I saw her today. That's impossible. She can't...
我今天还见过她 这不可能 她不能...
I'm sorry Lynn.
我很抱歉 林
The police ID'd her body.
警察确认了她的身份
My God.
我的天
If you need a phone
如果你需要电话
to make some personal calls or talk to the police...
来和家人联系或者 和警察谈谈的话...
Her boyfriend did this to her.
是她的男朋友干的
Tell me he's in custody.
告诉我他已经被拘押了
Is his name Dwayne Thompkins?
他是叫道温・托普金斯吗?
Yeah.
对
He didn't do it.
不是他干的
They found his body, too.
他们也发现了他的尸体
Lynn, the police are trying to make sense of something.
林 警察正在努力调查原因
Do you know if either your sister or her boyfriend
你知道你的妹妹或者她的男友
were involved in dealing drugs,
卷入了毒品交易
or had ties to.... organized crime?
或者和...有组织的犯罪有什么联系吗?
She was a... pretty serious user.
她是个...深度吸毒者
But organized crime... no way. Why?
但是有组织的犯罪...不可能  为什么这么问?
The killings were clearly the work of a professional.
很明显是职业杀手干的
Oh, my God.
我的天
I need to see preliminary forensics.
我想看看初步的调查结果
Who's investigating? I have to talk to them.
是谁在做调查? 我想跟他们谈谈
- I can arrange a meeting... - No, I have to talk to them now.
- 我无法安排见面...  - 不 我现在就要和他们谈
They have to search the apartment. See if my keycard's there.
他们必须搜查一下公寓 看看我的钥匙卡是不是在
What are you talking about? What keycard?
你说什么? 什么钥匙卡?
My CTU keycard! She has it, Bill!
我的CTU钥匙卡 她拿着 比尔
What was she doing with your keycard?
她拿你的钥匙卡干什么?
It was stolen from me, all right?
我的卡被偷走了 行了吧?
Her boyfriend took it.
她的男朋友拿走了
- Why didn't you report this? - I'm reporting it now!
- 你为什么不汇报?  - 我现在正在汇报
We don't have time to argue about this.
我们没有时间就此争吵了
Call and see if anybody used it to breach security.
打电话问问是否有人 用它通过了安检
It was taken about...
大概是...
about four hours ago.
是四小时之前被偷走了
O'Brian.
奥布赖恩
Chloe, I'm in Holding with Lynn.
科洛依 我跟林正在禁闭室
I need you to check the gate logs, now.
我要你立刻检查一下出入记录
What am I looking for?
检查什么?
Check and see if anyone used Lynn's keycard
查一下是否有人用林的钥匙卡
to enter CTU in the last four hours.
在过去的四小时内进入了CTU
Isn't Lynn standing right next to you?
林不就在你身边吗?
Chloe, do it!
科洛依 照做
Oh, my God.
我的天
It's showing that his card was used
记录显示他的卡在不到一小时之前
less than an hour ago at the executive entrance.
在行政人员入口处使用过
- He was already here... - Lockdown CTU now!
- 他已经进来了...  - 立刻封锁CTU
This is Chloe O'Brian. Initiate a lockdown now.
我是科洛依・奥布赖恩 立刻全面封锁
Mr. Bauer, I'm sorry. I don't know what's going on.
鲍尔先生 很抱歉 我不知道是怎么回事
He should be talking by now.
这个时候他早该开口了
Damn it, Christopher. It's enough.
见鬼 克里斯托夫  行了
I don't want to do this. Just talk to me!
我不想这么做 跟我说吧
I can't...
我不能说...
His vitals are crashing.
他的主要器官就快衰竭了
I need to stabilize him in the Clinic before administering another dose.
在打下一针之前 我必须把他送往医务室 让他的情况稳定下来
This is Bauer.
我是鲍尔
We've been compromised.
我们被渗透了
Someone used a stolen keycard
有人在不到一小时之前
to access CTU less than an hour ago.
拿偷来的钥匙卡进入了CTU
- Did you get an ID? - Not yet.
- 知道那人的身份吗?  - 还不知道
They didn't use the card to exit. They're still here.
他们还没用卡出去 他们还在这里
We're in lockdown, starting a search.
我们封锁了出入口 开始搜查
I'm on my way. Get him over to medical. Stabilize him.
我这就来 把他交给医务人员 让他稳定下来
Don't let anyone near him.
别让任何人靠近他
Did you get him?
找到他了么?
Still working on it.
还在找
Exits are sealed.
出口已经关闭了
Security cleared Third East, they're going room to room.
保安人员已经清查了东部3层 他们一间挨一间的搜查
Give me a comm unit.
给我个通话机
Audrey, is Kim still up in Field Ops?
奥黛丽 金还在外勤行动办公室吗?
With Landes, yes.
是的 跟兰德斯在一起
Get her down here. I want a guard on her.
让她下到这里来 我希望看住她
- I'm on it. - I think I got him in Third West.
- 我这就去办  - 我在三层西部发现了他
He's in processing.
他正在移动
Could exit south or north.
可能从南面或者北面离开这一层
Jack, take north. We'll give you updates.
杰克 去北面 我们会向你通报进展
Mac's team will head south.
马克这一组去南面
Copy that.
明白了
Pull up north and south angles.
调出南面和北面角度的监控录像
There he is.
看到他了
Edgar, run his face through recognition software.
埃德加 把他的脸放到辨认软件中去
Where's Carrie?
凯莉去哪儿了?
We need to check for grid intrusions.
我们需要查一下电力系统有没有被破坏
She's checking on a warning signal in a B-socket.
她去检查B插槽的一个警报信号了
Got it. Checking the grid.
明白了 检查电力系统
You're gonna help me get out of here.
你得帮我离开这里
- He's in the north corridor. - Chloe, cover for me.
- 他在北边的走廊  - 科洛依 替我一下
I want to see what's keeping Carrie.
我去看看凯莉被什么缠住了
- Go ahead. - All units,
- 去吧  - 所有人员注意
he's moving west in the north corridor.
他正在北面的走廊向西移动
He's got one of our men.
他挟持了我们一个人
Enter your passcode.
输入你的密码
But it's a lockdown!
可是现在已经封锁了
Just do it.
做就是了
He's in the north stairwell, sub-level B.
他在北面楼梯间地下B层那里
Jack, do you read?
杰克 听到了么?
I'm on my way.
我这就过去
Bill,
比尔
he's in the stairwell.
他在楼梯间吗?
I don't think so, Jack.
我想不会吧 杰克
Davis said he checked sub-level B.
戴维斯说他查过地下B层了
Bill...
比尔...
It was all clear.
没有情况
No, he's doubled back.
不 他又回去了
He's using the stairs to get the roof.
他走楼梯往楼顶去了
All right, Jack.
好吧 杰克
I'm sending you into the landings.
我派你去楼顶停机坪
Let me know when you're ready to move.
你准备好行动了就通知我
Copy that.
知道了
Freeze!
别动
Let me see your hands!
把你的手举起来
Slowly.
慢慢地
Drop the gun!
扔掉枪
Now!
快点
Bill, it's Jack. Hostile's down. He's dead.
比尔 我是杰克 目标被击毙
It was the only shot I had.
这是我唯一的选择
Do you have an ID, Jack?
弄清楚他的身份了么?
We've got a bigger problem than that.
我们遇到更麻烦的问题了
He's got a device on him. Looks like a relay switch.
他身上有一个装置  像是一个摇控开关
Hold on.
等一下
He's got a PDA.
他身上有个PDA
- Oh, my God. - What is it, Jack?
- 我的天  - 是什么 杰克?
It's a schematic of CTU's ventilation system.
是一张CTU通风系统的示意图
I think he tried to deploy nerve gas throughout the building.
我想他是要在这幢楼里释放神经毒气
Order an evacuation.
下令全体撤离
Code six!
6号警报
Everybody out!
所有人都快出去
Go! Go!
快走 快走
Jack, I have Kim with me.
杰克 金和我在一起
Stay with her. I'm on my way.
跟她一起 我马上就过来
Make sure Burke gets Henderson out of here as fast as he can.
让伯克尽快把亨德森转移出去
All right, I'm on it. Don't move. I'll be right back.
好的 我这就去 别走开 我马上回来
- O'Brian. - Chloe, what's going on?
- 奥布赖恩  - 科洛依 出什么事了?
Edgar, get out of the building now!
埃德加 赶快撤出这幢楼
Carrie?
凯莉?
We have to get out of the building now.
我们得马上从这幢楼里出去
- What's going on? - Just hurry!
- 出什么事了?  - 照办
What's wrong with those people?
这些人怎么了?
Oh, my God.
我的天
The nerve gas is making its way in. Go.
神经毒气扩散过来了 快走
The ducts run from the outside in.
气体是由外向里扩散
"Outside in"?! What does that mean?!
由外向里? 什么意思?
They start at the perimeter and reach the building core last.
气体释放于大楼的周边地区 最后会到达大楼的中心
Auto-lock the outer doors.
自动关闭外围的门
- Which rooms can we seal? - I'm working on it.
- 我们可以密封哪些房间?  - 我正在查
Burke, I need you to stand by.
伯克 你原地待命
We can't leave the building yet.
我们还不能离开这幢大楼
I'll let you know where you can move Henderson.
我会告诉你把亨德森转移去哪里
- Chloe, what rooms can we lock down? - Hold on!
- 科洛依 我们可以密封哪些房间?  - 等等
We can lock down the Situation Room,
我们可以密封局势研究室
the upper offices and Clinic Isolation.
高级职员的办公室和医务室的隔离病房
Go, people!
大家快走
Kim, everybody, in the Situation Room! Move now.
金 所有人  去局势研究室 快
I'll access Comm from my office!
我可以在我的办公室和你保持联络
Burke, you can move Henderson to the Clinic Isolation.
伯克 你可以把亨德森 转移到医务室的隔离病房
Seal it off for bio. I repeat: Seal it off for bio.
按生化武器级别进行密封 我重复一遍 按生化武器级别进行密封
Get in the Situation Room now.
快去局势研究室
Move!
快
Chloe, seal it. Seal all the rooms.
科洛依 密封 密封所有的房间
Open the door! You have to let me in! Open the door!
开门 你们得让我进去 开门
Oh, my God. Let her in!
上帝 让她进来吧
We can't break the seal.
我们不能打开封条
You have to try and find another exit out of the building.
你必须找另外的出口离开这里
Hurry! Go!
赶紧 走
Chloe, are the rest of the rooms sealed?
科洛依 其他房间密封好了么?
Yes, it's done.
是的 好了
Everybody, stay calm. There's nothing we can do for her now.
大家保持冷静 我们没有任何可以帮她的
Oh, no.
不是吧
Oh, my God.
我的天
Chloe.
科洛依